It's my life. It's your life.
Fighting for tomorrow.
Go get what you really want.
I want more. Any one more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life. It's your life.
Run like a wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your call.
Let's keep on going, I'll not stay.
Let's do it again, you
know what I mean, baby.
No one can make my dream come true!
Don't you feel it?
I really don't know what is
Something is testing me every day.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
I know I never wanna come back here.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away the great
end of the unknown rules.
Standing up, blowing up.
My dream is getting wilder.
I'm not afraid, beat me, hit me.
I will never turn around.
Another day, another chance.
You know it's never too late.
If I can do it, so can you only without.
It's my life, it's your life.
Party for tomorrow, go
get what you really want.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the door.
It's my life, it's your life.
Run like a wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you cannot achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going, roaring.
It's my life, it's your life.
Fighting for your life that I
want, but you're where it was.
I want more, and you want more.
Come on, open up the gate.
It's my life, it's your life.
Shine like a star to be good, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Just that you can't achieve your best.
Let's keep on going out of day.
You make my day every day.
What a low-down, rotten trick.
Cheating bastard.
Is he so scared of Lucy that
he had to change the rules?
We got to do something in the meantime.
We'll take down Doflamingo and
kiss that birdcage goodbye.
I made my message perfectly clear.
Either you bring me Straw Hat
or I kill you on the spot.
Gets, can we afford to wait on Lucy?
People are going to die if
we hold out much longer.
I'm aware of that, but I can't send a
fighter in his condition back into the ring.
Until he gets his Haki back,
he's under my protection.
Who is that?
Whoa!
It can't be! Trafalgar Law?
The Warlord?
Wait a sec.
I think you're running too far away.
Well, that's...
Because...
Straw Hat gonna get his Haki back or not?
Yeah,
it's just he said he
needed ten minutes and
now we've got about
three and a half to go.
I'll take him under my care from here.
Let's go.
Every second counts. Yes, sir.
Less than three minutes to go until the
walls of the birdcage close completely.
All right, guys, don't make me look bad.
Keep pushing in my period's gotcha.
Go!
We'll do it just like Mr. Zoro. Whoa!
Everybody's together now!
And push!
This is odd.
They were all terribly injured, but
now they're exerting so much strength.
A few moments ago, some of
them couldn't even stand,
let alone fight back
against something like this.
What were those fluffy things?
They're called dandelixers.
What are they? An ability.
Princess Monchory creates them.
They're healing flowers that
sprout up from her tears.
Wait, I can't run any faster!
You're going to have to or you'll die!
Come on, we don't want to leave you!
It's no use!
I twisted my ankle!
This is the best I can do!
Don't give up!
Okay, let's go!
Hey, I thought you twisted your ankle!
The Dandelixer Puffs can
heal people over a wide area.
Anywhere they fall, they
bring miraculous recovery.
Seeing the sad state that her home is in,
Princess Monchery is overwhelmed with
grief and overflowing with tears.
But her sorrow can save a
countless number of lives.
I see.
That's why the injured
fighters rose up again.
Unfortunately, the ability has a drawback.
Although everyone is strong and healthy
right now, the effect is temporary.
After three minutes have passed, everyone
will revert to their former state.
So it's a life support procedure designed
to see us through this final battle.
All of a sudden the pain just went away.
I can run again, that
means I don't have to die.
This is a miracle, it must be.
Someone up there in heaven is
looking out for our kingdom.
Hey, Cub.
Yes, Princess Monchery.
This is the only way that I can fight.
I don't know how to use any weapons.
And I can't stop the bad
guys, even though I want to.
All I have are these
tears that never stop.
You know, I actually think that's
a kind and honorable way to fight.
What happened?
Everyone's injuries are healing up!
We can figure it out later.
For now, let's run!
Not so fast!
Listen to what I have to say first!
yes hack what is it not him listen to me
the five-star guy got us
up so what was your crime
anyway shut up now this is the
deal if you're strong we need
your help in the east and west
my friends are there pushing
the bird cage back by force
this is the only way he really
thinks we can push back the
bird cage no way that's gonna
happen man that's crazy yeah
that's totally impossible trust
in my friends you won't know
until you try we made a god angry
we'll do our best you hear
that it's going to be all right
there are still people out there fighting
to save dress rosa come on you'll
be okay thanks rebecca they're fighting
the birdcage with all their might
But what if it can't be stopped?
No matter how strong they are, then
all their efforts will be in vain.
I know I can't fight as
well as someone like Lucy,
but still,
if everyone is laying their lives on
the line, I have to do whatever I can.
I'm sorry, Father, but there's
only one way to end this.
By killing the flamingo.
Viola! Rebeca!
What are you doing here?
I'm here to fight!
I have to!
That's ridiculous, and you know it.
If I let you join your mother,
I would never be able to face
Kiros again, as long as I lived.
So, what business do
you have with me, Viola?
The Don Quixote family is
about to be obliterated.
If I do nothing to take
responsibility as a former executive,
it would be an insult to this nation.
You can't!
Only one of us is going to
leave this battle alive, Dolphy.
Now face me!
You always were a woman of
passion, weren't you, Violet?
I've got a child! Let us through!
What's the holds up?
The birdcage is right there!
They said there's danger up ahead!
Nobody here is making any progress!
Everyone in the kingdom
was headed for downtown,
but now that we're here, we're stuck!
We gotta push way harder!
You got this little prose!
We're trying!
Stop this thing, I guarantee!
Now what are we gonna do?
We're all given place!
Is this a success?
I think it's slowed down
a little bit. Probably.
It is Snipe, but I
believe you are correct.
I don't have time for you sorry,
but I'm afraid you'll have
to tell me who's speaking.
I'm blind you see
Damn it.
Hard to turn my back on people in need.
Even if they are a bunch of fools.
Although my strength may be meager.
I shall devote it to
your cause all the same,
all right,
assist whoever you can
at pushing back the game.
Why we may survive those who can't
use Haki head to the factory?
The Navy is here!
Now let's push that factory!
It's coming! Run away!
Hey, don't stop! You're crazy!
If everyone runs away, how
will anything get fixed?
I'm pushing, too. What? Wait! Now push!
Damn it! Me too!
Check out these arms!
Yeah, that's the spirit!
Check my zoo!
We came here to help push!
This is our kingdom,
so we gotta protect it!
Mega Muscles coming through!
That's what I'd like to hear!
Now it's time to give
this everything you got!
There they are!
We might not be as strong as you
are, but we want to push too!
Then get up here and push! Alright!
Help me in.
I'm not getting chopped up without a bite.
You have my thanks.
Truly, of course.
It's the least we can do.
All right, you ready? Yeah!
Whatcha gonna do?
Hold!
Keep it up!
Time for round two!
Even if it started up again,
we didn't stop it. Mrs.
Zoro showed us the way.
Thank you for guiding us with your life.
Keep pushing.
We stopped it once and we'll do it again.
Everyone together now.
Time for a big push. Ready?
King Rick and Commander Tank?
Have you saved this kingdom yet?
You've done well so far.
If not for your efforts, we would have
lost thousands of our citizens already.
You can't keep people
in no birdcage, brother.
Don't you know that these
folks are born to be free?
And how are we going to prove it?
We're going to play!
Then what?
We push the war!
You're nothing, birdcage.
You can't stop us!
Viola, run! That's enough!
Please get up!
I know what you're thinking.
You spent ten years with
me as part of the family.
So surely I would hesitate for a
moment at least, before I killed you.
But you misunderstand my philosophy.
I don't punish my associates
for their failures.
I forgive them.
But betrayals are another matter entirely.
Don't worry.
You can play, too.
Look at your sweet Rebecca now, Violet.
No, my body—I can't control it.
What's she doing with that sword?
That doesn't look safe at all!
You bastard!
bastard
Good girl, come this way for me.
Leave her alone!
This battle's between you and me!
I can't...
I can't stop it!
Viola!
Keep fighting it!
I'm trying, but it's no use.
Very good.
Now kill Violet.
I'm so sorry.
I don't want this.
But he's too strong.
Rebecca!
Come on, stop.
Please forgive me.
It's made it all the way to the
old King's Plateau. Damn it.
There's not much city left.
People are going to start
dying one after another soon.
Keep pushing. This is it.
Even a second could save lives.
Hey. I lost count.
How much longer until
Lucy comes back? I...
I'm not sure.
The birdcage was halted for a moment,
but now it continues to close.
The time remaining is 60 seconds.
The time until Luffy
recovers is also 60 seconds.
We stopped it once, didn't we?
We'll do it again if we have to.
Get pushing!
Let's go!
You gotta remember what's at stake here.
Either you push or you die.
You're not helping. Just shut up.
We all got too many dreams to give up now.
No way we're gonna die.
Hooray!
Stacy, everybody, please.
We have all seen enough suffering.
Are you ready, everybody?
Huh?
It won't be much longer now!
Who's talking?
Where's that coming from?
Some kind of PA?
Our hero is on his way! Hey!
There he is!
That's Jax, isn't it?
The announcer from the Coliseum?
What are you doing up there?
He's lost it.
Surely you remember him.
Whatever this is, now is not the time.
The whole kingdom's about
to be destroyed, you know.
We'd rather hear from King Rick.
What that?
I need to remind you.
Unpredictable in nature and
irrepressible in spirit,
he burst onto the sea
and, more importantly,
into our hearts.
The hero who lit up the Coliseum
like a shining star! Shining star?
There's only one answer, surely.
He means me.
Hey, I know I said I'd
stay here with you, but...
Well, it turns out my fans need me. Sorry.
Hello! Trafalgar! What? Where did he go?
His courage.
Rocked my soul.
He tamed the savage bull that struck
fear into the hearts of all gladiators.
His fearsome fists fell
the giant even the living
legend Don Chinchao
faltered before his might.
Though small in stature, his energy
was felt through all of the coliseum.
No, through all of Dressrosa!
A man who was born to be free,
who fought perfectly, who struck
a chord in our hearts brilliantly.
Now are you with me?
Yeah, I saw him. That guy.
He was pretty amazing.
He blew me away, too.
Everyone in the city
was watching him fight.
You know his name?
Lucy!
What are you getting at?
How is a gladiator
supposed to save us now?
Please...
Lucy...
Please... Help me...
But Lucy was only an alien!
That's right!
He has another name you don't know!
Would you like to hear it?
He's a pirate.
Known as Straw Hat.
Monkey D.
Lukey
He sure had me fooled with that beard.
I understand your reservations.
You must be wary about
trusting another pirate.
When Doflamingo has been lying.
And grinding us under
his heel for so long.
However.
He's different from
the Don Quixote family.
who tried to pass themselves off as our
saviors that night so many years ago.
You don't have to trust me.
Instead, listen to King Rick, who
placed his faith in Straw Hat Luffy.
This is the call before the storm.
Lucy is taking a breather right
now in preparation for round two,
but he's going to come back even stronger.
So raise your hands in
celebration, Dressrosa.
Because I spoke to Lucy,
and he made me a promise.
He'll face Doflamingo!
And knock him out in one punch!
He sure talks big.
I'm making this quick, Captain.
Because I'm slipping.
Real fast.
I can't wait.
Hey, Joe Flamingo.
You hear that?
You phony.
Cheating our king.
Filling our streets with lies.
Sitting on a misbegotten throne.
Build on a mountain of injustice.
But now you must face your trial.
Your cruelty ends today.
Guts.
That's right, Doflamingo.
I see straight through you.
If you're mad, come and get me!
Keep your filthy hands
up, Viola and Rebecca.
And soon enough,
the Coliseum Shining Star,
our Lucy, will take the stage.
Let's show him how we feel
and give the man a cheer.
The Mr.
Lupin, let's go!
I wrote it!
What's wrong?
It's like their injuries
came back all of a sudden.
They're dropping like flies.
Because time has run out.
These people were the ones who
were given the dandelictures first,
and now they're wearing off.
And they aren't going to work twice.
I'm sorry.
That's the best thing to do.
I tried, but my ability
just didn't come enough.
I did such an awful thing.
I gave them a host, and I yanked it away.
That's not true, Princess Moncheree.
If it wasn't for your help,
there's no telling just how many lives
the birdcage might have claimed today.
Do you see?
You made a miracle happen down there.
Hey, come on!
Don't give up!
Clear out the injured and have the
people in the back take their place.
Bring in some fresh troops!
Roger!
We'll hold our ground at any cost until
Lucy gets rid of the birdcage for good!
They were able to stall it long enough.
Thanks to you, they'll survive
till Loopyland returns.
It won't be long now.
Let's begin the countdown
to Lucy's countdown.
Call out his name.
Make sure he can hear us.
Lose it!
Count from three!
Lose it! Lose it! Two!
Lose it!
Lose it! One!
What a joke.
Your time is up, Doflamingo.
Lucy's gonna knock you out cold.
One punch and you're toast.
And now, you can go quiet, too.
Forever, that is.
I'm sorry, Biela! Wake up, Rebecca!
Close your eyes!
You don't have to see a thing.
This is just a bad dream.
Once it's over, you can
strike it from your memory.
I'll forgive you.
All that matters is that you move on.
Please be happy.
Stop that!
Don't be upset.
It's not your fault.
I'm sorry I have to leave you like this.
I know it will hurt.
I know it won't be easy to overcome.
No!
Get back!
Lucy is here at last!
Lucy!
Lucy! Lucy!
Star-Hat!
This is all rather dramatic, isn't it?
But still, I imagine it took a
lot just to recover your Haki.
Why, it's probably a struggle
for you just to stand.
Maybe.
But you're no better off.
Lucy!
Samples.
Rebecca!
That's where you crawled off to.
Perfect.
You've got front row seats.
Now watch as I crush the
only hope you've got left.
Time forever, White!
They turned the whole block into strings!
Lucy!
Damn you!
It's no use.
Thousand arrows!
Flapping threat!
Now die!
Over me!
Done already.
What about your comeback, huh?
I'm not seeing that miraculous
Haki of yours, Lucy.
Is he gonna be okay?
That didn't look good Did Lucy win?
I can't tell.
The birdcage is still here.
Lucy, hurry!
What the hell?
My body's moving on its own.
I can't believe you
survived that last assault.
I'll have to inhale
you properly next time.
Or maybe I should force you to
kill all of your friends instead.
Ha, ha, ha, came running back
with your tail between your legs.
Well, you escaped death
again. That's good.
Next time, I'm gonna win!
Your famous Kong gun didn't do the trick.
This guy was huge!
Way bigger than the last one,
so the move didn't work, really!
It wasn't fair!
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
Sounds like you're in trouble, then.
Oh, well, if the kong gun doesn't work,
then you'll just have to
come up with something else.
I guess, but what?
It's almost tragic.
All those little insects were so much
better off dancing on their streams,
trapped in my cage as
they were meant to be.
Insects?
That's what you think?
Of course.
Humans are nothing but garbage.
That's enough already!
We're waiting, Lupi!
Hmph. Go ahead.
Turn into your stupid balloon man, Finn.
That'll be more fun for me.
I'll have you kill all your friends,
then kill everyone else in the
kingdom while you're at it.
Alright, fourth gear!
He cut them.
You can't have much strength remaining.
How long do you think
you can last in that war?
This is it!
Sure you want to challenge
someone like me in the air?
You got some nerve.
Still beating me in one hit?
Let's see it then.
I don't know if I like
you looking down on me.
Well, no matter.
I'll just have to drag you to the
ground and make you my puppet again.
Every time.
You just grab whatever
you want and strangle it!
You can't have everything!
You can't control everyone either!
Seeing you makes it hard to even breathe!
That's not my fault.
Blame your fate.
To be born as a human is
to be born as living trash.
It's my divine right to
control you as I please.
I'm gonna kick your ass.
Then everyone here will be free.
They'll be able to breathe again.
Kick my ass, then. Try it.
Fight a whip!
Oh, well.
If the Kong gun doesn't work, then you'll
just have to come up with something else.
Now, Kong-Kong!
I guess the what?
Something different.
Fourth gear is indeed strong,
but I'm afraid it taxes
your body too much.
Okay, then how about this?
What? No.
That would be even harder on you.
All right, King Kong!
All those who won't obey me must die.
My sixteen holy bullets
shall be your trial!
God Threat!
Ahhhhhhh!
Those who fear the inheritors of
D have given them another title,
sworn enemy of gods.
You